(window.webpackJsonp=window.webpackJsonp||[]).push([[0],[,,function(e){e.exports=[{category:"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",type:"multiple",difficulty:"hard",question:"What%20was%20the%20name%20of%20the%20hero%20in%20the%2080s%20animated%20video%20game%20%27Dragon%27s%20Lair%27%3F",correct_answer:"Dirk%20the%20Daring",incorrect_answers:["Arthur","Sir%20Toby%20Belch","Guy%20of%20Gisbourne"]},{category:"Animals",type:"multiple",difficulty:"easy",question:"What%20is%20the%20scientific%20name%20for%20modern%20day%20humans%3F",correct_answer:"Homo%20Sapiens",incorrect_answers:["Homo%20Ergaster","Homo%20Erectus","Homo%20Neanderthalensis"]},{category:"Entertainment%3A%20Books",type:"multiple",difficulty:"hard",question:"What%20is%20Ron%20Weasley%27s%20middle%20name%3F",correct_answer:"Bilius",incorrect_answers:["Arthur","John","Dominic"]},{category:"Entertainment%3A%20Comics",type:"multiple",difficulty:"easy",question:"Who%20is%20the%20creator%20of%20the%20comic%20series%20%22The%20Walking%20Dead%22%3F",correct_answer:"Robert%20Kirkman",incorrect_answers:["Stan%20Lee","Malcolm%20Wheeler-Nicholson","Robert%20Crumb"]},{category:"Entertainment%3A%20Board%20Games",type:"multiple",difficulty:"medium",question:"At%20the%20start%20of%20a%20standard%20game%20of%20the%20Monopoly%2C%20if%20you%20throw%20a%20double%20six%2C%20which%20square%20would%20you%20land%20on%3F",correct_answer:"Electric%20Company",incorrect_answers:["Water%20Works","Chance","Community%20Chest"]},{category:"Geography",type:"multiple",difficulty:"easy",question:"What%20is%20the%20capital%20of%20Jamaica%3F",correct_answer:"Kingston",incorrect_answers:["Rio%20de%20Janeiro","Dar%20es%20Salaam","Kano"]},{category:"History",type:"multiple",difficulty:"medium",question:"When%20did%20Jamaica%20recieve%20its%20independence%20from%20England%3F%20",correct_answer:"1962",incorrect_answers:["1492","1963","1987"]},{category:"Animals",type:"boolean",difficulty:"easy",question:"Kangaroos%20keep%20food%20in%20their%20pouches%20next%20to%20their%20children.",correct_answer:"False",incorrect_answers:["True"]},{category:"General%20Knowledge",type:"multiple",difficulty:"medium",question:"In%202013%20how%20much%20money%20was%20lost%20by%20Nigerian%20scams%3F",correct_answer:"%2412.7%20Billion",incorrect_answers:["%2495%20Million","%24956%20Million","%242.7%20Billion"]},{category:"History",type:"multiple",difficulty:"medium",question:"How%20old%20was%20Lyndon%20B.%20Johnson%20when%20he%20assumed%20the%20role%20of%20President%20of%20the%20United%20States%3F",correct_answer:"55",incorrect_answers:["50","60","54"]},{category:"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",type:"multiple",difficulty:"hard",question:"In%20World%20of%20Warcraft%20lore%2C%20who%20organized%20the%20creation%20of%20the%20Paladins%3F",correct_answer:"Alonsus%20Faol",incorrect_answers:["Uther%20the%20Lightbringer","Alexandros%20Mograine","Sargeras%2C%20The%20Daemon%20Lord"]},{category:"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",type:"boolean",difficulty:"medium",question:"In%20the%20game%20%22Subnautica%22%2C%20a%20%22Cave%20Crawler%22%20will%20attack%20you.",correct_answer:"True",incorrect_answers:["False"]},{category:"Entertainment%3A%20Japanese%20Anime%20%26%20Manga",type:"multiple",difficulty:"medium",question:"What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20the%20device%20that%20allows%20for%20infinite%20energy%20in%20the%20anime%20%22Dimension%20W%22%3F",correct_answer:"Coils",incorrect_answers:["Wires","Collectors","Tesla"]},{category:"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",type:"multiple",difficulty:"medium",question:"What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20Cream%20the%20Rabbit%27s%20mom%20in%20the%20%22Sonic%20the%20Hedgehog%22%20series%3F",correct_answer:"Vanilla",incorrect_answers:["Peach","Strawberry","Mint"]},{category:"History",type:"multiple",difficulty:"easy",question:"These%20two%20countries%20held%20a%20commonwealth%20from%20the%2016th%20to%2018th%20century.",correct_answer:"Poland%20and%20Lithuania",incorrect_answers:["Hutu%20and%20Rwanda","North%20Korea%20and%20South%20Korea","Bangladesh%20and%20Bhutan"]},{category:"Entertainment%3A%20Television",type:"multiple",difficulty:"hard",question:"Which%20of%20these%20voices%20wasn%27t%20a%20choice%20for%20the%20House%20AI%20in%20%22The%20Simpsons%20Treehouse%20of%20Horror%22%20short%2C%20House%20of%20Whacks%3F",correct_answer:"George%20Clooney",incorrect_answers:["Matthew%20Perry","Dennis%20Miller","Pierce%20Brosnan"]},{category:"Entertainment%3A%20Music",type:"multiple",difficulty:"medium",question:"From%20which%20album%20is%20the%20Gorillaz%20song%2C%20%22On%20Melancholy%20Hill%22%20featured%20in%3F",correct_answer:"Plastic%20Beach",incorrect_answers:["Demon%20Days","Humanz","The%20Fall"]},{category:"General%20Knowledge",type:"boolean",difficulty:"easy",question:"Scotland%20voted%20to%20become%20an%20independent%20country%20during%20the%20referendum%20from%20September%202014.",correct_answer:"False",incorrect_answers:["True"]},{category:"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",type:"multiple",difficulty:"medium",question:"In%20Left%204%20Dead%2C%20which%20campaign%20has%20the%20protagonists%20going%20through%20a%20subway%20in%20order%20to%20reach%20a%20hospital%20for%20evacuation%3F",correct_answer:"No%20Mercy",incorrect_answers:["Subway%20Sprint","Hospital%20Havoc","Blood%20Harvest"]},{category:"History",type:"multiple",difficulty:"hard",question:"What%20was%20the%20last%20colony%20the%20UK%20ceded%20marking%20the%20end%20of%20the%20British%20Empire%3F",correct_answer:"Hong%20Kong",incorrect_answers:["India","Australia","Ireland"]}]},,,,function(e,t,r){e.exports=r(13)},,,,,function(e,t,r){},function(e,t,r){},function(e,t,r){"use strict";r.r(t);var n=r(0),a=r.n(n),o=r(4),i=r.n(o),s=(r(11),r(1)),c=(r(12),function(e){var t=e.questionNumber,r=e.totalNumOfQuestions,n=t/r*100;return a.a.createElement("div",{className:"progress"},a.a.createElement("div",{className:"progress-bar questionNumber",role:"progressbar","aria-valuemin":"0","aria-valuemax":r.toString(),style:{width:"".concat(n,"%")}}))}),l=r(5),u=function(e){var t=e.numOfQuestionsAnswered,r=e.numOfCorrectAnswers,n=e.numOfWrongAnswers,o=e.totalNumOfQuestions,i=(r/o*100).toFixed(2),s=0===t?0:Math.ceil(r/t*100),c=Math.floor((o-n)/o*100);return a.a.createElement("div",{className:"tracker"},a.a.createElement("p",{className:"score"},a.a.createElement("span",null,"Score: ".concat(s,"%")),a.a.createElement("span",null,"Max Score: ".concat(c,"%"))),a.a.createElement("div",{className:"progress"},a.a.createElement("div",{className:"progress-bar leastPossibleScore",role:"progressbar",style:{width:"".concat(i,"%")}}),a.a.createElement("div",{className:"progress-bar currentScore",role:"progressbar",style:{width:"".concat(s-i,"%")}}," "),a.a.createElement("div",{className:"progress-bar  highestPossibleScore",role:"progressbar",style:{width:"".concat(c-s,"%")}})))};var m=function(e){var t,r=e.questionNumber,o=e.totalNumOfQuestions,i=e.selectedQuestion,c=e.correctAnswerIndex,m=e.showNextQuestion,d=Object(n.useState)(null),h=Object(s.a)(d,2),f=h[0],y=h[1],w=Object(n.useState)(!1),p=Object(s.a)(w,2),g=p[0],b=p[1],E=Object(n.useState)(0),_=Object(s.a)(E,2),v=_[0],N=_[1],A=Object(n.useState)(0),q=Object(s.a)(A,2),S=q[0],C=q[1],O=Object(n.useState)(0),W=Object(s.a)(O,2),F=W[0],k=W[1],H=Object(n.useRef)();null===f&&(t=""),!0===f&&(t="Correct!"),!1===f&&(t="Sorry!");var M=decodeURIComponent(i.category),x=decodeURIComponent(i.question),B=function(e,t,r,n,a){e===t?(y(!0),C(function(e){return e+1})):(y(!1),k(function(e){return e+1}),H.current.classList.add("correctAnswer")),N(function(e){return e+1}),r.target.classList.add("clicked"),b(n!==a),document.querySelectorAll(".button").forEach(function(e){e.disabled=!0})};return a.a.createElement("div",{className:"container "},a.a.createElement("h2",null,"Question ".concat(r," of ").concat(o)),a.a.createElement("h5",null,M),a.a.createElement("h6",null,function(e){var t,r=[];"hard"===e&&(t=3),"medium"===e&&(t=2),"easy"===e&&(t=1);for(var n=0;n<t;n++)r.push(a.a.createElement("i",{key:n,className:"bi bi-star-fill"}));return r}(i.difficulty)),a.a.createElement("h4",null,x),a.a.createElement("div",{className:"options"},function(){var e=decodeURIComponent(i.correct_answer),t=i.incorrect_answers.map(function(t){var n=decodeURIComponent(t);return a.a.createElement("button",{onClick:function(t){return B(n,e,t,r,o)},className:"button"},n)}),n=Object(l.a)(t);return n.splice(c,0,a.a.createElement("button",{ref:H,onClick:function(t){return B(e,e,t,r,o)},className:"button"},e)),n}()),a.a.createElement("div",{className:"correct text-center"},a.a.createElement("h2",{className:"result"},t),g&&a.a.createElement("button",{onClick:function(){m(),y(null),document.querySelectorAll(".button").forEach(function(e){e.disabled=!1}),b(!1),H.current.classList.remove("correctAnswer"),document.querySelector(".clicked").classList.remove("clicked")},className:"next"},"Next question")),a.a.createElement(u,{numOfQuestionsAnswered:v,numOfCorrectAnswers:S,numOfWrongAnswers:F,totalNumOfQuestions:o}))},d=r(2);var h=function(){var e=Object(n.useState)(1),t=Object(s.a)(e,2),r=t[0],o=t[1],i=Math.floor(4*Math.random());return a.a.createElement("div",null,a.a.createElement(c,{questionNumber:r,totalNumOfQuestions:d.length}),a.a.createElement(m,{selectedQuestion:d[r-1],totalNumOfQuestions:d.length,questionNumber:r,correctAnswerIndex:i,showNextQuestion:function(){o(function(e){return e+1})}}))};Boolean("localhost"===window.location.hostname||"[::1]"===window.location.hostname||window.location.hostname.match(/^127(?:\.(?:25[0-5]|2[0-4][0-9]|[01]?[0-9][0-9]?)){3}$/));i.a.render(a.a.createElement(h,null),document.getElementById("root")),"serviceWorker"in navigator&&navigator.serviceWorker.ready.then(function(e){e.unregister()})}],[[6,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.acc1b3ee.chunk.js.map